CURRICULUM VITAE

Kapil Kasliwal

Telephone No. : 0141-2220917, (M) 9983900077

E mail : kasliwal1875@gmail.com

Summary

20+ yrs. of Administration experience, across varied industries like Insurance, Telecom, BPO and Training Institutes. My strengths Good Communication, Dedication, Strong Commitment towards my job and Strong Public Relation, helps me in effective manpower & resource management besides serving and motivating the teams working and associated with the organization. My skills include Database management, Vendor management, Administration at all front and my proficiencies are MIS, Documentation, Liaison with authorities / industry associates.

Work Experience

Poonawalla Fincorp Ltd From 9th July'14 – Till date

Position : Sr .Manager- Regional Admin Manager-Rajasthan

Responsibilities include:

- Look after all verticals of Administration-for Rajasthan Region looking after 27 branches of Rajasthan. All verticals includes Projects/Real Estate/ Facility management
- Look after Property finalization/Lease agreement/Fit out work and Infra management.
- Managing admin budgets, finalization of yearly admin budgets for the Rajasthan region, managing quarterly budgets and monitoring and evaluate expenses on regular basis.
- Look after office and infra management proper up keep of electrical equipment, timely renewal of AMC's of all critical equipments.
- Looking after the Housekeeping and security aspects.
- Liasioning with all the govt bodies
- Look after all necessary statutory compliance of all Rajasthan branches
- Looking after vendor management for Rajasthan Region, ensure proper quality vendors for all admin utility services.
- Coordinating with other regions of north in terms of data management, MIS management, coordinating for various admin facilities related activities

•

Work Experience

Reliance Communication Ltd

From 5th September'13 – 7th July 2014

Position: Manager- Administration Rajasthan Circle

Responsibilities include:

- Look after all verticals of Administration-Projects/Real Estate/Facility Management
- Look after Property finalization/Lease agreement/Fit out work and Infra management.
- Look after project vendors/infra vendors.
- Managing admin budgets, finalization of yearly AOP for the circle, managing quarterly budgets and monitoring and evaluate expenses on

- regular basis.
- Look after cafeteria management; ensure proper hygiene and quality food & beverages to be served.
- Look after office and infra management proper up keep of electrical equipment, timely renewal of AMC's of all critical equipments.
- Taking care of employee engagement programs.
- Looking after the Housekeeping and security aspects.
- Taking care of all the Logistics activities.
- Maintaining and upkeep of company guest house
- Looking after the interiors of Circle Office.
- Liasioning with all the govt bodies

Etisalat DB Telecom Pvt Ltd.

From 22nd September'09 – 16th August'12

Position: Asst. Manager – Administration(Raj./Gujarat)

Responsibilities include:

- New Circle rollout. Taking care of all the HR and Admin functions functions, like- Man power recruitment, office management & infrastructure management
- Look after all verticals of Administration-Projects/Real Estate/Facility Management
- Hired properties for Rajasthan circle.
- Look after Property finalization/Lease agreement/Fit out work and Infra management.
- Look after project vendors/infra vendors.
- Taking care of employee engagement programs.
- Maintenance of Data Bank comprising of all employee related activities (Mediclaims, Claims, Service records, Duty records, Attendance, Statutory requirements)
- Looking after the Housekeeping and security aspects.
- Taking care of all the Logistics activities.
- Organizing various training programs for the self development of employees.
- Maintaining and upkeep of company guest house
- Looking after the interiors of Circle Office.
- Handling the cab management for whole Rajasthan. Ensuring of proper taxi services for the technical and project team..
- Handling all the statutory compliances related to labour laws.
- Liasioning with all the govt bodies

Tata AIG Life Insurance Co. Ltd.

From 14 January'08 – 20th September'09

Position: Asst. Manager – Facilities & Projects

Responsibilities include:

- Looking after Facilities & Projects of Rajasthan Region
- Involved in property selection/property finalization for up-coming branches.
- Lease Deed finalization, lease registration of new branches.
- Co-ordination with vendors to complete project work on time to meet target live date.
- Handling facilities and R&M related issues for 28 branches (Rajasthan Region).
- Vendor Management.
- Processing of restacking requests.

- Co-ordination with team for the renewal of S&E license on time.
- AMC of all critical equipments.
- Co-ordination with F&A for timely release of payments (vendor bills/LL rentals).
- To ensure that all registers are maintained properly as per processes.
- To keep an eye on outsource service providers to ensure the best service delivery.
- Ensure proper housekeeping and security of all branches across Rajasthan through outsource agency.

Idea Mobile Communication Ltd, Rajasthan Circle.

FromFeb2006- Dec 2007 Position: Sr.Executive Admin Responsibilities include:

- New Circle rollout. Taking care of all the HR and Admin functions functions, like- Man power recruitment, office management & infrastructure management
- Look after all aspects administration which includes Projects/Real Estate/Facility management.
- Identifying new properties for office, property finalization/lease agreements/Fit out work of all properties.
- Short listing of candidates, organizing interviews.
- Taking care of employee engagement programs.
- Maintenance of Data Bank comprising of all employee related activities (PF, Mediclaims, Claims, Service records, Duty records, Attendance, Salary compilation, Statutory requirements)
- Looking after the Housekeeping and security aspects.
- Taking care of all the Logistics activities.
- Organizing various training programmes for the self development of employees.
- Maintaining and upkeep of company guest house
- Looking after the interiors of Circle Office.
- Handling the cab management for whole Rajasthan. Ensuring of proper taxi services for the technical and project team..
- Handling all the statutory compliances related to labour laws.
- Liasioning with all the govt bodies
- Deployment of Security Guards at various sites across Rajasthan.

Airtel-Broadband & Telephone Services

Since March 2005- Feb2006 Position: Executive Admin Responsibilities include:

- General HR and administration functions, like- Man power recruitment, office management & infrastructure management
- Short listing of candidates, organizing interviews.
- Back office activities of HR department
- Taking care of employee engagement programs.
- office management & infrastructure management
- Purchase and Inventory Management
- Looking after the Housekeeping and security aspects.
- Taking care of all the Logistics activities.
- Vendor selection for Jaipur office.

•

• Taking care of complete aspects of Administration

Supportscape India Pvt. Ltd. From June 2000 to December 2004

Position: Assistant Manager – Administration

Responsibilities include:

- General administration and all HR functions
- Recruitment of manpower for the various departments.
- Shortlisting of candidates, organizing interviews for various levels
- Organizing various training programmes.
- Front Desk Management, Housekeeping & Security
- Looking after purchase and stock management
- Maintaining stock registers, audit of stock and inventory
- Liasioning with government departments like STPI, Excise, Labour Department, DOT, VSNL.
- Administering payroll activities. Salary administration, Liasioning with and submission of reports to ESI and PF departments
- Coordinating between accounts department and all staff in matters related like TDS, calculation of taxes, etc.
- Taking care all the attendance related issues
- Pick and drop facility, canteen facility, shift rostering of agents & route planning
- Back office activities of HR departments, motivational exercises, events management & conferences
- Taking care of client's visit, hotel reservations pick up and drop facilities for the clients.

CIStems Software Ltd. Jaipur From December 1997 to May 2000 Position: Administrative Officer Responsibilities includes:

- Looking after the after-sales service department of CIStems School of Computing a division of CIStems Software ltd.
- Fee collection, Batch allotment, Faculty arrangement.
- Conducting of exams, result declaration
- Participation in business development activities like trade fairs, seminars, quiz competitions, event management, etc.
- Library management.

Professional Qualification

One year diploma in computers from Aptech Computer Institute.

Academic Qualification

1996 Graduated in Commerce from University of Rajasthan

1993 Completed 10+2 from Maheshwari Higher Sec. School, Jaipur

1991 Completed matriculation from Central Academy, Jaipur

Personal

Date of Birth : 18th December 1975

Address: 18, Ratnapuri, Ajmer Road, Jaipur-302019

Tele : 0141-2220917, (M) 9983900077 **E mail** : kasliwal1875@gmail.com

Marital Status : Married